老歌99.2
Oldies 99.2
这个地区的周末天气预报看起来不错
Well, the weekend forecast looking good for the area.
从布伦特伍德一直到里奇蒙
Sunny skies on tap from brentwood all the way north to Richmond...
以及整个维吉尼亚州都是晴空万里
最高气温达摄氏29度
and throughout the state of Virginia, with highs reaching 85 degrees.
晚上最低气温大约摄氏18度
Low tonight, about 65.
这个周末应该很适合登山客出去玩
Should be a great weekend for hikers to get out and enjoy...
你女儿真漂亮
Pretty girl.
你一定为她骄傲
You must be one proud papa.
这个黑人是谁
Who's the black fella?
达瑞斯克莱蒙斯  是她男朋友
Darius clemmons. It's her boyfriend.
他们和一群朋友一起旅行
They were traveling with a group of their friends.
阿帕拉契山路范围很广
Well, the appalachian trail's a hefty piece of real estate.
从缅因州一直到乔治亚州
I mean, Maine clear down to Georgia way.
我一直在追踪他们的路线
I've been tracking their route,
她答应每周给我打电话或发简讯
and she promised to call or text every week.
已经有六周了
And it's been six weeks.
她最后一次给我发简讯是在你们镇上
The last place that she texted me was here in your town.
其实来这里的孩子太多了
Well, the fact is we get a shit-ton of kids that come through here.
他们来了  做了他们想做的  然后离开
I mean, they come, and they do whatever it is they do, and they move on.
我儿子在坦帕的乡村摇滚乐团玩键盘
My boy's down in tampa playing keyboard in some rockabilly band.
我都不记得那孩子
上次和我通电话是什么时候了
I can't remember the last time that boy picked up a phone.
我女儿不是那样的人
My daughter's not like that.
如果你愿意  我们可以正式一点
Well, we can make it official if you'd like.
填一下这份失踪人口报告
Fill out this missing persons report.
你想怎么写  就怎么写
Be as detailed as you'd like.
如果是我  我打赌
But if I were to put money on it,
我觉得她在某个小岛晒太阳呢
I'd say she's somewhere sunning herself in the keys.
客人退房是自动的  我很少看到他们离开
Guest checkout is automatic. I rarely see them leave.
大部分在日出前就走了  想赶上飞机或避开塞车
Most are gone by sun up, trying to catch flights or beat traffic.
房间里什么都没有吗
And there was nothing left in the room?
没有  他们的车也不见了
No. And their car was gone.
好吧
Okay, well,
如果你想到什么请给我打电话  好吗
if you think of anything, please give me a call, yeah?
我叫史考特
My name's Scott.
你跟警长讲过了?
You spoke to the police chief?
是啊
Yeah.
我觉得  他认为这没什么
I didn't sense much urgency from him.
这是个宁静的小镇
This is a quiet town.
越宁静他钓鱼就钓得越多
The quieter it is, the more he gets to fish.
嘿  我是珍
Hey, it's Jen.
请留言我会回电  谢谢  拜
Leave a message, and I'll hit you back. Thanks, bye.
再看看  拜托
Look again. Please.
不  抱歉  不
No, sorry, no.
你知道有多少游客来这里吗
You know how many tourists come through here?
我记得的是酒  不是脸
I remember drinks, not faces.
丢东西了吗
Lose something?
我的女儿
My daughter.
她叫珍妮弗
Her name is Jennifer.
她和五个朋友经过这里
She passed through here with five of her friends.
他们年龄差不多
They're all about the same age.
我见过他们
Yeah, I seen 'em.
该死的屁孩
Goddamn yuppies.
你有注意到他们往哪边走了吗
You didn't happen to notice which way they went?
北边吧
North, maybe.
去上面
Up on the at.
但如果他们在树林里迷路了  你还不如回家
But if they got lost in them woods, you might as well just go on home,
因为你永远也找不到他们
'cause you ain't never gonna find 'em.
是啊
Yeah, well...
我才不信呢  我不信
I don't believe that. I can't.
随你怎么想  先生  但你要知道
Believe what you want, mister. But know this...
在外面
Out there,
大自然会吞噬掉所有能抓住的东西
nature eats everything it catches right down to the bone.
根本不在乎是不是个可爱的女孩
Doesn't give a shit if it's a cute girl.
你有孩子吗
Do you have kids?
你会怎么做
What would you do?
(六星期前)
(欢迎光临维吉尼亚州)
你觉得这张怎么样
What do you think of this one?
挺好
Yeah, it's-it's fine.
亚当  看看  什么  搞什么
Adam, come on. What? What the fuck?
我需要用手机  我想给你看照片
I need that. I want to show you the picture.
把手机给我  不
Give me my phone. No!
嘿  宝贝你没事的
Hey. Babe, you're fine.
深呼吸
Just breathe.
敞开心扉
Open your mind.
好好享受  好吗
Enjoy it, okay?
看那个  我一直看起来就那么死臭脸吗
Look at that one. Is that how sad I look all the time?
是的  没错
Yes, you do, actually.
我一定很爱你
I must really love you.
是的  真奇怪你这么爱
You really do. It's-it's weird how much you love...
你真奇怪
You're weird.
吻我
Now kiss me.
哇哦  啊
Whoa! Ah!
你这样让我很难堪
You know, uh, you're making me look bad.
抱歉  不用担心  这才是女权
Sorry. Don't be. Fucking girl power.
女权
Girl power.
女孩你在哪学的
Dude, where'd you learn how to do this?
我爸
My dad.
他教会了我两件事
He taught me two things:
怎么做鱼饵  怎么换轮胎
How to bait a hook and how to change a tire.
我爸教我怎么塞卫生棉条
My dad taught me how to put in a tampon.
单身父亲
Single parent.
他一直闭着眼睛
His eyes were closed the whole time.
这可不是什么好经历
Not a good experience.
哦
Oh.
可以了  太好了
Oh, here we go. Sweet.
珍  珍  珍
Jen, Jen, Jen.
我的英雄
My fucking hero.
这真古典
It's quaint.
是啊  尤其是如果你怀念邦联的美好时光
Yeah, especially if you miss the good old days of the confederacy.
好吧
All right.
这个是我的
This one's mine.
那是你的  宝贝  拿你的
That's yours, babe. Trying to grab yours.
把我的给我
Pass me mine.
三间房  两晚是的
Three rooms for two nights. Yes.
旅馆的规章制度都贴在你们的房间里
Policies of the inn are posted in your rooms.
露台上不准喝酒
No alcohol on the patio.
房间里不准点蜡烛  不准放大声的音乐或吵闹
No candles in the room, no loud music or raucous activity.
听到了吗  男孩们  规矩点
Hear that, boys? Behave yourselves.
谢谢  别担心  我会管好他们的
Thanks. And don't worry. I'll keep them on a short leash.
你以前来过这里吗
Have you been here before?
我第一次来  只是徒步旅行
First time. Just doing a little hiking.
给你个建议  沿着标记的路走
Piece of advice, keep to the marked trail.
这里的土地是残酷无情的
The land here can be unforgiving.
谢谢  我们会小心的
Thanks. We'll be careful.
你知道有一群废奴主义者  是来自这个镇上吗
You know that a bunch of abolitionists came from this town?
达瑞斯喜欢那东西  该死的历史  宝贝
Darius loves that shit. Fucking history, baby.
那时人们还在为自己的信仰而战
Back when people actually fought for what they believed in.
对了那是什么  之前那是什么
Listen, by the way, what was that... What was that thing earlier?
你为什么不牵我的手
Why wouldn't you hold my hand?
没什么  没有原因
Nothing. No reason.
这是有原因的
Oh, there's a reason.
和达瑞斯紧张的原因一样
Same reason Darius is on edge.
亚当  老兄弟
Adam. Dude.
什么  他是个黑人有个白人女友
What? He's a black dude with a white girlfriend
在维吉尼亚州
in bum-fuck Virginia.
嘿
Hey.
你们不是本地人吧
Y'all ain't from around here, are you?
是什么暴露了我们
What gave us away?
是的
Uh, yeah.
我们只是来看看阿帕拉契山路
We're just, uh, checking out the appalachian trail.
徒步旅行几天  没什么特别的
Couple days of hiking. Nothing extreme.
上面有危险的东西
There's something dangerous up there.
如果你有任何问题或需要指导
So if you got any questions or you need a guide,
我和我的朋友们  我们对这片土地
me and my pals over here, we, uh, we know this land
无比了解
like the back of our hands.
谢谢谢谢  我想我们不用
Thanks. Thanks. I think we're good.
这是你的决定
It's your life.
但如果你改变主意了
But, uh, if you change your mind...
我们随叫随到
We'll always be around.
开着一辆破皮卡喝着私酿烈酒  对吧
Driving around in a shitty pickup, sipping moonshine, am I right?
别说了
Stop it.
你说什么  啄木鸟
What'd you say, peckerwood?
请原谅我的未婚夫
Excuse my fiancee.
他忘了跟人聊天和在网路上当键盘侠不一样
He forgets that talking to people isn't like commenting on reddit.
别看我  小子
Don't look at me, boy.
你们这些屁孩  就是这个世界的问题所在
You goddamn hipster freaks are the problem with this whole world.
我打赌你们中没有一个人
I'm betting not a goddamn one of you
做过真正的工作
ever worked a real fucking job in your life.
所以你们最好乖乖坐着
So you better sit the fuck still and behave yourself.
你错了
You're wrong.
珍
Jen.
我男朋友达瑞斯经营一家非盈利  公益环保能源机构
My boyfriend, Darius, runs a sustainable energy nonprofit.
米拉是个肿瘤学家  亚当是个软件开发人员
Milla's an oncologist. Adam's an app developer.
盖瑞和路易斯在纽约开了一家小酒馆
And Gary and Luis own a pair of New York bistros.
我会称这些为真正的工作
I don't know. I'd call those real jobs.
那你呢  亲爱的
And what about you, sweetheart?
我有两个硕士学位
I have two master's.
艺术史和舞蹈
Art history and dance.
也就是说  我以煮咖啡为生
Which means I make coffee for a living.
但现在我看着你
But right now I'm looking at you,
我看到你眼睛发黄了
and I'm seeing some yellowing in your eyes.
看这有什么问题  米拉
Which means what, Milla? Hmm?
可能是肝脏问题
Oh, um, it could be liver problems.
像是吉伯特氏症候群(黄疸)  肝炎等
Jaundice, hepatitis, Gilbert syndrome.
你应该去看医生
You should probably see a doctor, actually.
好吧
All right, well...
孩子们  注意安全
You kids be safe.
也许我们还会再见面
Maybe we'll see you again.
说真的  别再这样了
Seriously, do not do that ever again.
我受不了  老兄  我们为什么让你喝酒
I can't handle that. Dude, why do we let you drink?
因为通常我都很搞笑
Because usually I'm very funny.
不  事实上你从来都不搞笑
No, actually, you have never, ever been funny.
从来都不
Like, never.
酒呢
Where are the drinks?
你知道这首歌
You know this song.
你知道吗
Do you know this?
不  但这是首好歌
No, but it's a good song.
好了  各位  早上八点准时出发
Okay, people, 8:00 A.M.
路易斯  盖瑞  我在跟你们说话
Luis, Gary, I'm talking to you.
好吧  我不喜欢早起
Okay, I'm not a morning person.
如果我不能睡满8小时  我就会变成僵尸
If I don't get my eight hours, I will be a zombie.
那就当一个徒步旅行的僵尸  嘿  各位
Be a zombie who hikes. Hey, guys.
伙伴们  怎么了
Guys. What?
车旁边的是谁
Who's that by the car?
那是酒吧里的混蛋吗
Is that one of those assholes from the bar?
可能吧
Yeah, probably.
嘿  亚当
Hey. Adam.
别冲动  嘿
Relax. Hey!
离车远点
Get away from the car, man.
离那里远点走开
Get away from there. Shoo.
他不是狗  喂
He's not a dog. Yo!
你是聋了还是怎么了  给我退后
Are you deaf or something? Back the fuck off!
天啊  亚当你是想惹毛这里所有的人吗
Jesus, Adam, are you trying to piss off everyone in middle America?
你得对这些人强硬点
You gotta be tough with these people.
好了  大块头该睡觉了
Okay, big guy, time for bed.
来吧  帮我壮胆
Come on. Back me up here.
亚当
Adam.
算了吧
Come on, forget about it.
那家伙跑哪去了
Where the hell did that guy go?
来吧
Come on.
你好  我是史考特
Hi this is Scott.
请留言  我会尽快回复谢谢
Leave a message and I'll get right back to you. Thank you.
老爸  抱歉这么晚打给你
Hey, dad. Sorry to call so late.
我们还在阿帕拉契山路徒步旅行
We're still hiking the appalachian trail.
等我回来  我保证会告诉你
When I get back, I promise I'll give you an answer
我的计划
about what I plan to do.
我爱你
I love you.
跟科琳打个招呼
Say hi to Corinne.
也许她会跟你打个招呼
Maybe she'll say hi back for a change.
好的  回头聊
Okay, talk soon.
拜
Bye.
亚当说得对吗
So is Adam right?
你紧张吗
Are you on edge?
我们现在就可以回家
We can go home right now.
想得美  但你可以不用保护我
Hey, nice try, but you don't have to protect me.
你知道我为什么在环保能源机构工作
而不是华尔街吗
You know why I work in nonprofit instead of on wall street?
因为
Because...
我想建立一个社区
I want to build a community where people are valued
在那里重视的是人们的才能和性格
on their skills and their character.
不是他们的银行存款或肤色
Not their bank account or their skin color.
大家都有工作
Everyone works.
大家分享
Everyone shares.
我愿为此付出一切
I'd give anything for that.
我知道
I know.
所以我才爱你
That's why I love you.
真漂亮  这些都是你做的吗
These are beautiful. Did you make all this?
有一些
Some.
嘿
Hey.
我是珍  你叫什么名字
I'm Jen. What's your name?
别介意露丝
Don't mind ruthie.
她不喜欢说话
She don't like to talk.
我在她这个年纪也很害羞
I was shy too at her age.
她是你女儿吗  算是吧
Is she yours? In a manner.
养孩子需要全村人的努力  不是吗
It takes a village to raise a child, isn't that what they say?
多少钱
How much?
十块钱
Ten dollars.
谢谢
Thanks.
早安
Good morning.
我真的从没见过你穿这件
I've literally never seen you wear this.
哇哦  好
Wow. Wow. Okay.
是啊
Yeah!
害羞之行
Walk of shame.
你们好啊  我和盖瑞要去远足
Hey, what's up, you guys? Me and Gary are going on a hike.
我不知道你在拍
I didn't know that you were filming.
大家都到了是的  是一个YouTube影片
Everyone's here. Yeah, it's for a YouTube video.
(阿帕拉契山径  往南  往北)
背我
Catch me.
我的天啊  救命啊
Oh, my god! Help!
真漂亮  大自然
Oh, it's beautiful. Nature.
昨晚还有人喝醉了吗
Is anyone still drunk from last night?
混球  是我
Bitch, I am.
最后一杯不是个好主意
That last shot was a bad idea.
等等  看来这条路到头了
Wait, looks like the trail ends.
我们是往这边走  还是往那边走
Are we going this way, or are we going this way?
你手机有信号吗
Do you have signal on your phone?
没有
No.
我有  我的信号太差了
I can do that. I've been horrible.
瞧瞧啊  太他妈棒了
Look at that. This is fucking awesome!
喔
Whoo!
去上面
It's up here.
没事吧
Okay?
你知道我们要去哪吗
Do you know where we're going?
我不知道
I don't.
你知道我们要去哪吗
Do you know where we're going?
好了伙伴们  来个快速小旅行
Okay, quick little side trip, guys.
什么  这附近应该有
What? There's supposed to be
保存完好的内战要塞
a very well-preserved civil war fort near here.
不错嘛  我们去找吧
Cool. Let's find it.
旅馆的女人说我们不该离开小路
Um, the woman at the inn said we shouldn't leave the trail.
只是随便看看
It's just a quick look around.
宝贝  如果什么都找不到
我们就回到小路上来
Babe, if we don't find anything, we'll just cut back over to the trail.
你知道如果我们沿着小路走  会发现什么吗
You know what we wouldn't have found if we would have stayed on the trail?
嗯  瀑布
Hmm? The waterfall.
悬崖呢
And that cliff, hmm?
来吧  我们会没事的
Come on. We'll be good.
好  好吗
Okay. Okay?
她答应了
She said yes!
喔  喔  来吧
Whoo! Whoo! Let's do it.
什么意思  他们要结婚了吗
What does that mean? They getting married?
等等  这只是徒步旅行  对吧
Wait, just for the hike, right?
你还好吗
You good?
真是个徒步旅行者
Such a hiker.
怎么回事
What was that?
一条蛇  我的天啊
A snake. Oh, my god.
你没事吧  没事
You okay? Yeah.
我们没事
We're good.
妈的  谢谢  干
Shit. Yeah, thanks. Fuck.
啊
Ah!
你没事吧  嗯哼
You okay? Uh-huh.
达瑞斯  还要多久
Dar, how much longer is this gonna take?
再往前一点好吗  我保证  好吗
Look, it's just a little further, okay? I promise, okay?
拜托
Please.
你没事吧  不好啦
You okay? No!
我们得走了  我们要继续前进
We got to go. We got to keep going.
我们走了他妈几个小时了
We've been walking for fucking hours.
那就是我们都一直在走
That's what we've been doing.
我们已经走了超一个多小时了
We've been walking way more than an hour.
好像走了四个小时了  你在说什么呢?
What are you talking about? It's been like four hours.
四个小时  不  我的意思是
Four hours? No, I mean...
我是说自从我们通过了那东西
I mean, since we passed that thing.
知道吗
You know what?
你们何不回到小路上去
Why don't you guys just, um, just head back to the trail.
我们上面见
I'll meet you guys up there.
那是什么
What is that?
我的天啊  亚当
Oh, my god! Adam!
我的天啊  快快快快
Oh, my god! Go, go, go, go, go.
你们往左跑
You guys, move left!
亚当
Adam?
米拉
Milla. Hey.
你抛下了我
You left me.
什么  你抛下了我
What? You left me.
我知道  我知道  我很抱歉  好吗
I know. I know. I'm sorry, okay?
我吓坏了  我不知道自己在做什么
I was freaking out. I didn't know what I was doing.
你抛下了我  我知道我很抱歉
You left Mel I know. I'm sorry.
你抛下了我
You left me!
拜托  别再这样了
Please, don't do that again!
我很抱歉  好吗
I'm so sorry, okay?
过来
Come here.
我操
Oh, fuck.
珍  珍
Jen? Jen?
Jen! Jen!
你没事吧
Are you okay?
你没事吧  没事
Are you okay? Yeah.
天啊  达瑞斯  你的手指
Oh, my god, Darius! Your finger!
我操
Oh, fuck!
我们没事  操
We're okay. Oh, fuck.
路易斯和盖瑞呢
Where's Luis and Gary?
嗯
Huh?
天啊
Oh, shit.
路易斯  路易斯  离开
Luis. Luis, man. Get out of here.
来吧  我们去那边  来吧
Come on. Let's go over here. Come on.
不  不  不  不
No, no, no, no.
不  不不  我们去那边
No, no! No! Let's go over here.
别他妈碰我
Do not fucking touch me!
可以
Okay.
不  不  不
No, no, no.
我操
Oh, fucking shit.
我们需要求助
We need to call for help.
我找不到手机了
I can't... I can't find my phone.
我找不到手机了  帮我找到它
I can't find my phone. Help me find it.
我操  没信号
Oh, fuck. No service.
我们得去高处
We need to go to higher ground.
我要爬上去打个电话
I'm going to climb up and try and make a call.
我们不可能再上去了  好吗
There's no way we're going to go back up there, okay?
我会找路绕上去  怎么绕上去
I'll find a way around. What fucking way around?
珍  这是我的错
Not by yourself. Jen... this is my fault.
当然了  都是你的错
It goddamn is. It is your goddamn fault!
路易斯
Luis! Hey! Hey!
这不是任何人的错好吗
是达瑞斯把树弄下来的吗
It's nobody's fault, okay? Did Darius make the tree fall?
看着我  是达瑞斯把树弄下来的吗  不是
Look at me. Did Darius make the tree fall? No.
这太他妈的狗屎  好吗
但这不是任何人的错  好吗
This is fucking awful, okay? But it's nobody's fault, okay?
路易斯  对不起  我真的对不起
Luis, I'm sorry, man! I'm fucking sorry, man!
我自己去  我现在就去
I'll go by myself. I'll go right now.
我们都得去
We all have to go.
什么  我不能丢下他
Why? I can't leave him.
要下雨了  看起来马上要下雨了
If it rains, which it looks like it's about to...
我们暴露在外  伙伴们
We're exposed out here, guys.
这个斜坡不安全
This slope's not safe.
我觉得上面有人
I think... I think someone's up there.
什么  上面有人
What? Someone's up there.
我没看到任何人  他们在哪
I don't... I don't see anyone. Where are they?
我看到了一个人  我看到了  我看到了一个人
I saw someone. I did. I-l saw someone.
该死的
This is so fucked up.
我看到了一个人
I saw someone.
没事的
It's okay.
去他妈的  去他妈的
Fuck this. Fuck this!
你没事吧
You okay?
谢谢
Thanks.
不客气
No problem.
他不会在这里太久的
He won't be here long.
没有人会承认
No one's gonna admit it.
是我就会
So I will.
我们迷路了
We're lost!
承认吧  达瑞斯
Just admit it, Darius.
完全不知道我们在哪  嘿  嘿  我们没事
No fucking clue where we are. Hey. Hey. We're fine.
我们要穿过这座山
We're-we're cutting across the mountain,
最终我们会到达另一边
and eventually, we'll hit the at on the other side.
但我觉得我们可以在外面过夜
But I think that we can probably camp out for the night.
我不会把盖瑞留在树林里过夜
I'm not leaving Gary out there in the woods overnight
让动物  昆虫或任何他妈鬼东西去给他啃
for animals and insects and whatever the fuck!
那已经不是盖瑞了
That's not Gary anymore.
路易斯  那只是个尸体
Luis, that was his body.
他的灵魂已经升天了
His spirit's moved on.
他也是这么想的  对吧
That's what he believed, right?
他现在在天堂  他很开心
He's in paradise now. He's happy.
过来  伙伴
Come here, man.
好吗
Okay?
好
Okay.
你能拉一下这个吗
Can you pull this?
我操
Oh, fuck.
谢天谢地雨停了
Thank god it stopped raining.
米拉呢
Where's Milla?
嗯
Hmm?
我没感觉到她起来了
I-1 didn't feel her get up.
她可能去哪尿尿了
She probably went somewhere to pee.
米拉
Milla?
上帝啊
Jesus.
我们一直睡在墓地里
We've been sleeping in a graveyard.
伙伴们  过来看看
Hey, guys, come check this out.
什么
What?
看这个
I ook at this.
这是一份宣言  承诺建立美国
This is a declaration pledge to the foundation of America.
你是说邦联
You mean the confederacy.
奴隶制万岁
Long live slavery.
不  实际上这是战前的
Uh, no, actually, this is... Dated before the war.
1859年11月24日
"November 24, 1859."
这里列出了十几个家庭
There's like a dozen families listed here,
献出自己和孩子的生命
pledging their lives and their-their children's lives.
嘿  你们谁拿了我的手机
Hey, did one of you take my phone?
没有
Um... no.
也许昨天出事的时候你掉了
Maybe you dropped it yesterday when everything was happening.
(在真诚基础上建立幸福理想的美国)
不不  我昨晚把它放回包里了
No, no, I-I put it back in my pack last night.
我的手机也不在这里
Mine's not here either.
米拉回来了吗  没有
Did Milla come back? No.
你手机呢  什么
Hey, do you have your phone? What?
妈的
Shit.
我们的手机呢
Where's our fucking phones?
好  我们的手机都没了
Okay, all our phones are gone.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck is going on?
我昨晚好像看到帐篷外有人
I thought I saw somebody outside the tent last night.
什么  什么
What? What?
什么时候  大半夜
When? In the middle of the night.
就出现一下下
Just for a second.
可能只是树影
Could have just been shadows from the trees.
操
Fuck!
你们帮我找到米拉
You guys, help me... help me find Milla.
亚当  她肯定没事
Adam... I'm sure she's fine.
你说树滚下来后  你有看到人
You thought you saw someone after the tree fell,
昨晚又看到了  现在我们的手机都没了
and then again last night, and now our fucking phones are gone.
他们现在可能正在监视我们
They're probably fucking watching us right now!
不不不  我答应过她不会再抛下她了
No, no, no, no, I promised her that I wouldn't fucking leave her again.
我他妈答应过她
I fucking promised her that.
亚当亚当
Hey, Adam! Adam!
米拉
Milla!
米拉  米拉
Milla! Milla!
米拉
Milla!
Milla?
米拉  米拉
Milla! Milla!
米拉
Milla!
嘿
Hey.
米拉
Milla!
你在这里干什么  米拉
What are you doing out here? Milla!
那是谁
Who's that?
我在镇上见过她
I saw her in town.
她好像叫露丝
I think her name's ruthie.
在镇上吗
In town?
嘿
Hey!
嘿  对不起
Hey. Sorry.
过来一下  你为什么不过来一下
Come here. Why don't you come here for a second.
我想问你点事  亚当
Adam. I just wanna ask you something.
不  你看到这个女孩了吗
她突然出现  米拉不见了
No, you see this girl, and now she's here out of fucking nowhere, and Milla's gone?
你觉得这是巧合吗
You think that this is a coincidence?
不可能  别激动
No fucking way. Calm down.
我他妈警告过你  小心那些白人乡巴佬
I fucking warned you about these white-trash hillbillies.
亚当  停下
Hey! Adam! Stop!
快过来
Get over here!
嘿  嘿
Hey! Hey!
亚当  嘿
Adam. Hey!
停下  嘿  嘿  嘿  嘿
Stop. Hey, hey, hey, hey.
亚当
Adam.
不不不  别让她跑了
No, no, no, no, no! Don't let her get away!
达瑞斯  去  追她  不等等
Dar, go on after her! No, wait!
什么
What?
伙伴们  伙伴们  那是什么
Guys? Guys, what is that?
我的脚被什么东西锁住了
My foot's caught on something.
什么鬼东西
What the hell is that?
伙伴们  哇哦
Guys! Whoa!
这什么鬼东西
What the hell is this?
哇哦  哇哦  哇哦  达瑞斯
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Darius!
怎么回事  伙伴们  达瑞斯  帮帮忙
What's going on? Guys? Darius, help!
什么  什么
What? What?
亚当  我的天啊
Adam! Oh, my god!
不不不
No, no, no, no, no, no!
亚当
Adam?
能听见我说话吗
Can you hear me?
亚当  你看到他了吗
Adam! Do you see him?
没有
No.
我感到一股气流
Uh, I-I feel a draft.
路易斯  抓住我的腿
Luis, grab my legs.
把我放下去好吗
Lower me in, okay?
亚当
Adam!
Adam...
亚当
Adam.
干  他妈的
Oh, fuck! Shit! Shit!
达瑞斯  这太疯狂了  我们需要求助
Darius, this is crazy. We need help.
如果我能把那条蛇弄出来
Look, if I can get that snake out of there,
也许我能找到亚当  然后呢
maybe I can reach Adam, okay. And do what?
他还被铁链缠住了  如果他受伤了怎么办
He's still caught on that chain. What if he's hurt?
也许这个洞和旧矿井相连
Maybe this hole connects to an old mine or something.
我们可以找个入口  然后
We can look for an entrance, and then...
好吧  你想找多久  一个小时  两个小时  整天
Okay, how long do you want to look? An hour? Two? All day?
那条铁链肯定通向某个地方
That chain goes somewhere!
我知道  有人放在那里的
I know! Somebody put it there.
你听到我说的了吗
Do you hear what I'm saying?
我们得下山求助
We need to get the fuck off this mountain and get help.
没有手机  没有全球定位系统
No phones. No GPS.
我们要怎么找到这里
How are we supposed to find our way back here, huh?
珍  你在干什么
Jen, what the hell are you doing?
走吧
Let's go.
这是什么地方
What is this place?
看起来像是整座山的失物招领处
Looks like a lost and found for the whole mountain.
我觉得亚当对这些人的看法是对的
I think maybe Adam was right about these people.
我们该走了
We should go.
伙伴们  走走走
Guys, guys, shh. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
是他们吗
Is that them?
镇上的那些猎人  我不知道
Those hunters from town? I don't know.
我不能
Can't...
那是亚当
That's Adam.
达瑞斯  不要
Darius, no.
嘿  嘿  马上把他放下
Hey, hey. Put him down right now.
把他放下
Put him the fuck down!
嘿  嘿嘿  嘿  我听不懂
Hey, hey, hey, hey. I don't understand.
说英语
Speak english.
天啊  亚当  他死了吗
Oh, my god, Adam. Is he dead?
我们的朋友呢
Hey, where's our friend?
我们的朋友呢  你把她带走了吗  你有吗
Where's our friend? Did you take her? Did you?
是你杀了她吗  回答我
Did you kill her? Answer me!
她在哪里  你做了什么
你他妈把她带走了吗  嘿
Where is she? What'd you do? Did you fucking take her? Hey!
我他妈要杀了你  退后
I will fucking kill you! Back up!
给我退后
Get the fuck back!
她在哪里  你对她做了什么
Where is she? What did you do with her?
她在哪里  她到底在哪
Where is she? Where the fuck is she?
我他妈听不懂你在说什么
I can't fucking understand you.
说英语  说英语
Speak english! Speak english!
你杀了她  你杀了她  你杀了她
You killed her! You killed her! You killed her!
亚当  亚当  你杀了她
Adam! Adam! You killed her!
亚当  亚当
Hey, hey, hey. Adam, Adam.
亚当  亚当  妈的
Adam, Adam, Adam. Shit.
妈的
Shit.
另一个呢  妈的
Where's the other one? Oh, shit.
他不见了
He's gone.
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
我别无选择
I had to.
他们
They...
他们杀了米拉  他们
They killed Milla. They...
他们杀了她
They killed her.
亚当
Adam.
亚当  我的天啊
Adam. Oh, my god.
你们怎么了
What happened to you guys?
这到底是怎么回事  怎么回事
What the hell's going on here? What's going...
那是什么  这他妈是怎么回事
What is that? What the fuck is going on?
操
Fuck.
那他妈是什么  伙伴们
What the fuck is that, guys?
怎么搞的
What happened?
你还活着
You're alive.
对  我还活着  这是怎么回事
Yes. I'm alive. What is this?
你去哪里了
Where have you been?
我去尿尿了  我在树林里
I left to go pee. I was in the woods.
我看到了两个大块头  他们穿成这样
I saw these two huge guys. They were... they were dressed like this.
所以我躲在灌木丛里
So I hid in the bush.
我们去找过你  你没听到我们叫你吗
We went looking for you. Didn't you hear us calling?
但我没办法回应  不然他们会听到
Yeah, but I couldn't answer back, or else they'd hear me.
他们走的时候  你们都走了
By the time they left, you had all gone.
宝贝  你怎么了  我以为你死了
Babe, what happened to you? I thought you were dead.
米拉  我们以为他们把你带走了
Milla, we thought that they'd taken you,
或是杀了你
or-or-or killed you or something.
你无缘无故杀了这个人吗
Did you just kill this man for no reason?
无缘无故
No-no reason?
他们把我拖进了一个洞里
They dragged me into a fucking hole,
把我像圣诞火鸡一样捆起来
trussed me up like a goddamn Christmas Turkey.
谁知道他们会对我做什么
Who knows what they were going to do to me?
我们只知道你刚刚杀了人
All we know for sure is that you just killed someone.
他们要杀了我  好吗
They were going to kill me, okay?
看看他  他就是个畜生
Look at him. He's a... He's a fucking animal.
他说得对  听我说听我说
He's right. Listen, listen.
地上躺着一个死人  另一个还活着
There's one fucking dead guy on the ground, the other one left.
我们不知道还有多少人
We don't know how many more there are.
我们得离开这座山  对吧
We have to get the fuck off of this mountain, right?
那尸体怎么办
What about the body?
是啊  怎么办  我们抛下了盖瑞
Yeah, what about it? I mean, we left Gary.
是啊  等我们回到镇上  我们就让警察
Yeah. When we get back to town, we'll let the fucking police
处理好这件事  不  去他妈的
handle this shit. No, fuck that.
想得美  我不会把自己交给某个乡巴佬法官
No way. I-i-l am not turning myself over to some redneck judge.
不  去他妈的  我们从没来过这里
No, fuck that. We-we-we were never here.
我们从没来过这里
We were never here.
所以我们就这样一走了之吗
So we just walk away from this?
对
Yes.
另一个呢  他看到我们了
What about the other one? He saw us.
哦  另一个  看起来很友好的那个
Oh, the other one. The really friendly-looking one
戴着骷髅面具  然后在说着方言
with the skull mask that was... that was speaking tongues?
他肯定是市议会的常客
Yeah, I'm sure he's a regular at city council meetings.
哥们  听着听我说  他们要杀了我
Dude, listen. Hey, hey, listen. They were gonna kill me!
听着  我知道他们没有杀米拉
Listen, okay, I get it. They didn't kill Milla.
但是设陷阱和工寮里面的东西  对吧
But the-the-the snare trap and the lumber mill, right?
还有亚当被绑在木头上  是的  是的
And Adam tied to a fucking log? Yes, yes.
谁他妈知道结果呢  他们可能杀了盖瑞
I mean, who fucking knows? They probably killed Gary.
这些人显然不是好人
Like, these are clearly not good people.
我们得离开这里  伙伴们
We got to get the fuck out of here, guys.
来吧  我们走走吧  来吧
Come on, let's go. Let's go. Come on.
来吧
Come on.
我们还往东走
We're still headed east.
一旦我们找到一条小溪  就能顺着它下山
Once we find a stream, we can follow it down the mountain.
我们直接下去吧
Why don't we just go straight down?
你想从悬崖上摔下去吗  请便
You want to take a header off a cliff? Be my guest.
好吧  你不用这么贱  我懂了
Okay, you don't have to be a fucking bitch about it. I get it.
都是我的错  我应该说我要去尿尿的
It's my fault. I should've announced I was leaving to go pee.
没事的  算了
It's okay. Forget it. Fuck.
我们应该把刚才看到的登山装备拿过来的
We should've grabbed some of that climbing gear we saw.
不  我们幸好什么都没碰对吧  不留痕迹
No, it's good we didn't touch anything, right? No traces?
如果我们没做错什么  就没什么好隐瞒的
If we've done nothing wrong, we have nothing to hide.
天啊  别装的跟正义警察说的鬼话一样  珍
Jesus, fucking quit it with the morality police bullshit, Jen.
你根本不知道自己想要什么
You're clueless about what you want
作为你那幸福的美国白人女孩的生活
for your own blessed all-American white girl life,
你确定知道其他人到底要的是什么吗？
and yet you know exactly what's right for everybody else?
我不是这个意思  是吗
That's not what I'm saying. Really?
我们真的不知道对错吗
Do we honestly not know what's right and wrong here?
对错那是你家的事  与别人无关
What's right for you has nothing to do with anyone else.
对的事就应该是对的  就这样
What's right should be right, period.
听着  轮不到你来说
Look... It's not for you to say.
那家伙死了  结束了
The guy's dead. It's over.
我们不会告诉任何人  好吗
We're not talking about it to anybody, all right?
随便
Whatever.
不如我们都闭嘴放松一下吧
Hey, how about we all just shut up and relax?
看看我们能不能做到
Let's see if we can make that happen.
操
Fuck.
老天爷啊
Jesus Christ.
我的天啊  达瑞斯
Oh, my god! Darius!
你没事吧  你没事吧
Are you okay? Are you okay?
又一个陷阱
Another fucking trap.
还觉得那些人不是怪物吗
Still think these people aren't monsters?
好吧  没那么糟
Ooh, okay. It's not that bad.
你该庆幸没伤到动脉
You're lucky you didn't tear an artery.
从哪来的
Where'd it come from?
肯定是踩到什么东西触发的
Must've stepped on something to trigger it.
妈的鬼地方
Fuck this place.
再次  感谢
Thanks... again.
再次  不客气
You're welcome. Again.
完好如初
Good as new.
走吧
Let's go.
路易斯
Luis?
他在哪
Where is he?
路易斯  路易斯
Luis? Luis?
我的天啊
Oh, my god.
路易斯  路易斯
Luis? Luis?
路易斯
Luis?
伙伴们
Guys?
天啊  是他们
Oh, god, it's them.
是他们
It's them.
伙伴  那里没人
Dude, there's nobody there.
伙伴们  是他们
Guys, it's them.
那里没人  别紧张别紧张  伙伴们
There's nobody there, man. Relax. Relax. Guys?
不  是他们  我们现在就得走  我们得走了
No, it's fucking them! We have to go right now. We have to go!
亚当  等等  米拉
Adam! Wait, no, Milla.
该死
Oh, shit.
快跑  快跑
Run. Run!
快跑  亚当
Run, run, run. Adam!
快快快
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
亚当
Adam!
米拉
Milla!
该死
Oh, shit.
亚当  帮帮我  米拉
Adam, help me. Milla.
天啊
Holy shit.
米拉
Milla.
把我弄出去  我的天啊
Get me out of here. Oh, my god.
好吧
Uh, okay.
救命  该死
Help. Oh, shit.
米拉
Milla.
快点
Hurry.
见鬼
Shit. Shit.
操
Fuck.
我马上回来  不  不要
I'll be right back. No, don't.
我去找人帮忙  我马上回来
I'm gonna get some help. I'll be right back.
不  你不能再抛弃我了  我去找人帮忙
No, you can't do this again! I'm just going to go get help.
我会回来的好吗  别丢下我看着我
I'm going to be back, okay? Don't leave me! Look at me!
他妈的看着我
Fucking look at me!
我操  不  去你妈的
Fuck. No! Fuck you!
你答应过我永远不会抛弃我
You promised me you would never leave me.
帮我
Help me.
来吧  我们走
Come on, let's go.
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck was that?
啊  达瑞斯
Ah! Darius!
达瑞斯  达瑞斯
Darius! Darius!
达瑞斯
Darius?
早安
Good morning.
你要迟到了  今天要坐你的车喔
You're late. And you're carpool today.
我知道  我有约
I know. I have class.
我要去萨德尔河见米尔本的
I got a meeting in saddle river with a roofer
一个屋顶工和一个混凝土工
and a concrete guy in millburn.
嘿  嘿
Hey. Hey.
你有珍的消息吗  她为什么要打给我
You haven't heard from Jen, have you? Why would she call me?
因为你是她妈妈  别说妈妈
Because you're her mom. Don't say "mom."
她讨厌这样叫  拿上你的东西  给你一分钟
She hates that. Get your stuff. You have one minute.
珍妮  我是爸爸
Jenny, it's your dad.
我再打来看看你怎么样
I'm, uh, just calling again to see how you're doing.
希望你和朋友玩得开心
I hope you're having fun with your friends.
听着我想跟你谈谈那个提议
Listen, I'd love to talk to you about that offer.
你会有自己的办公室和咖啡机
You'd get your own office and your own coffee maker
享有所有的福利
with all the perks.
我说真的
Excuse the pun.
总之
Anyhow...
别忘了给我打电话  好吗
Don't forget to call me, all right?
已经好几周了
It's been a couple weeks now, and...
我想听听你的声音
I'd love to hear your voice.
请给我回个电话
Please, give me a call.
谢谢  我爱你  拜
Thank you. I love you. Bye.
奇怪
Weird.
又转到语音信箱了
It went to voicemail again.
想知道她为什么不打电话吗
Want to know why she doesn't call?
珍妮弗去寻找自我了
Jennifer went off to find herself,
这是她为了逃避而做出的选择
which is a choice she made to avoid making a choice.
你能不能把注意力放在我的孩子们身上
Look, how about you focus on my boys, our boys?
就一次
For once.
是啊  求你了
Yeah. Please?
救命啊
Help!
救命啊  谁来救救我
Help! Somebody, please!
救命啊
Help me!
别叫了  不然你会受罪的
Stop your screaming, or you'll suffer for it.
你  我认识你
You. I know you.
救命啊  请帮帮我
Help me. Please help me.
你想吃东西吗  喝水呢
Do you want food? Water?
是的  那就闭嘴
Yes. Then shut your mouth.
明白吗
Understand?
求你了放我走吧
Please, please, please, let me go.
拜托  你在镇上见过我记得吗
Please. You met me in town, remember?
你和那个小女孩露丝  你很不听话
You and the little girl? Ruthie? You don't want to listen.
不不不  我很抱歉
No. No, no, no, no, no, no, no! I'm sorry!
我很抱歉  拜托
I'm sorry. Please.
求你了回来吧
Please, please come back.
拜托
Please!
这不可能
This isn't happening.
This isn't happening!
米拉呢
Milla?
快走
Walk.
搞什么
What the...
快走
Walk.
跪下
Kneel.
我受够了
I'm done with this bullshit.
跪下
Kneel.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
上帝啊  他们会杀了你的
Jesus. They'll kill you, man.
趴下
Stay down.
退后
Stay back.
天啊
Oh, god.
这是法庭
This is court.
你们正在受审
You are on trial.
受审  为了什么
Trial? For what?
谋杀
Murder.
真是胡扯  我们没有杀人
This is bullshit! We didn't murder anybody!
只有你能开口
Only you will speak.
如果你有问题  我女儿会回答的
If you have questions, my daughter will answer.
你不能让我们受审  这里不是法庭
You-you can't put us on trial. This-this isn't a court of law.
法庭就是法庭
The law is the law.
只有真相和谎言
There's only truth and lies.
这不可能  这不可能
This can't be happening. This can't be happening.
太他妈离谱了
It's fucking insane!
下一个说错话的人就会失去舌头
The next one who speaks out of turn loses their tongue.
霍布斯
Hobbs.
我看到他们每个人  在镇上和山上
I saw each of them, in town and on the mountain.
这个朝我扔瓶子
That one threw a bottle at me.
不  不  天啊  亚当
No, no. Jesus, Adam.
他说我们坏话
He says vile words about us.
他恨我们
He hates us.
摩根
Morgan.
Morgan...
告诉我们你看到了什么
Tell us what you saw.
山缪
Samuel...
他在说什么
W-w-what is he saying?
我哥哥山缪和我出去打猎了
"My brother, Samuel, and I were out hunting."
为过冬存粮而跟踪驼鹿和麋鹿
"Stalking moose and elk for the winter larder."
我们在检查洞穴里的捕猎陷阱
将捉到的猎物拖进洞穴
"We were checking our game traps in the cave where caught game is dragged
以防止其他猎食者靠近
to keep predators from getting to it."
啊  亚当
Ah! Adam!
我们发现了这个陌生人
"And we found this stranger instead."
他受伤了  昏过去了  我们要带他下山
"He was hurt, knocked out. We were taking him down the mountain."
打算把他留在被发现的地方
"Planned to leave him where he'd be found..."
当其他人跟我们起冲突的时候
"When these others attacked us."
他杀了我哥哥山缪
"He killed my brother Samuel."
不  我们不知道
No. We didn't know.
他们戴着动物头骨
They were wearing skulls,
身体披着树叶  还有血迹
and their bodies were covered with leaves and blood.
不然我们打猎时要怎么穿
What we wear when we go hunting, huh?
不就是隐藏我们的气味和样貌  不被猎物发现
To hide our scent and our faces from our prey.
你们打猎时也一样
Your hunters do the same.
嗯
Hmm?
他做了摩根指控的事吗
Did he do what Morgan has accused?
是这个人杀了摩根的哥哥山缪吗
Did this man murder Morgan's brother, Samuel?
敢撒谎  恐惧会降临在你们每个人身上
Lie, and dread will fall on each of you.
我警告你
I warn you.
说实话
Speak true.
不
No.
他没有杀他
He didn't murder him.
露丝
Ruthie.
露丝  谁杀了山缪
Ruthie, who killed Samuel?
你对法庭撒谎了
You lied to this court.
不  不
No, no.
亚当担心自己的生命安全
Adam feared for his life.
他出于自卫杀了这个人
He killed this man in self-defense.
这不是谋杀
It's not murder.
我们以为他们绑架了他
We thought they were kidnapping him.
我们以为他们要带他去某个地方杀了他
We thought they were taking him somewhere to kill him.
为什么  你为什么会这么想
Why? Why did you think this?
你有什么证据
What proof did you have?
你见过我们的人吗
Had you met any of our people?
我们伤害过你吗
Had we caused you any harm?!
本庭宣判你谋杀罪名成立
This court finds you guilty of murder.
判决是死刑  什么
The sentence is death. What?
不  不  不  我没有  那是误会
No, no, no, I didn't... It was a mistake.
我不知道他们在做什么
I didn't know what they were doing.
这不是我的错
It's not my fault!
退后
Gget back.
你想让这孩子跟你哥哥一起死吗
You want this kid to join your brother?
那就给我退后
Then back the fuck off!
亚当亚当  不
Adam, Adam, no.
闭嘴  亚当
Shut up. Hey, hey, Adam.
如果你伤害了她  我们的处境都会更糟
If you hurt her, you make things worse for all of us.
看看周围  达瑞斯  情况已经更糟了
Look around, dar. This shit's already worse.
好吧  你要这么做
Okay, this is what you're gonna do.
你要给我的朋友松绑然后放我们走
You're going to untie my friends, and then you're going to let us go.
我才不怕你
I'm not afraid of you!
我只想尽可能离你们这些混蛋鬼地方
I just want to get as far away from you backwoods fucks
越远越好
as I possibly can.
走开
Now, move.
我看着你的眼睛
I look in your eyes.
我只看到了恐惧
I see only fear.
你这样的人没有未来
There's no future for men like you.
去你妈的
Fuck you!
我不该叫你男人
I was wrong to call you a man.
其他人因作伪证而有罪
The rest of you are guilty for bearing false witness.
判决是黑暗
The sentence is darkness.
什么  不不不求你了求你了
What? No, no, no. Please, please.
带走  求你了  不要
Take them. Please, please, no.
求你了  不要不
Please, no! No!
珍  珍
Jen! Jen!
珍
Jen!
这个家庭应该受到惩罚
This family is owed retribution.
山缪是怎么被杀的
How was Samuel murdered?
说出来
Say the words.
山缪是怎么被杀的
How was Samuel murdered?
他的头被打
He was struck in the head.
用这个
With this.
不不不
No, no, no, no, no.
不  别这样
No, don't do this.
别这样  求你了
Don't do this, please.
求你了这是不对的
Please. It's wrong.
这太野蛮了
It's barbaric.
听我说  听我说
Listen to me, listen to me.
我们可以帮你
We can help you.
我们什么都愿意做
We'll do anything.
我们可以给你钱  你说太野蛮了?
We can get you money... Barbaric?
我们的家族建造了这个地方
Our families built this place.
不同种族  不同信仰的男男女女来到这里
Men and women of all races and creeds
是为了躲避即将降临两国之间的世界末日
came here to avoid the armageddon they knew was coming between the states.
我们需要的都有了
We have everything we need.
大家都在工作  每个人都有贡献
Everyone works. Everyone contributes.
我们的食物新鲜充足
Our food is fresh and plentiful.
我们没有癌症没有贫穷没有战争
We have no cancer, no poverty, no war.
不会因为你有  而我没有  所以彼此怨恨
No one hates another because they have while another doesn't.
我们是生命共同体的
We are one body working together.
你告诉我  谁的世界更野蛮?
You tell me, whose world is more barbaric?
不
Nol
带走
Take them.
你的判决是黑暗
Your sentence is darkness.
在这里  你看不到恶
Here, you will see no evil,
听不见恶  说不出恶
hear no evil, speak no evil.
不
No!
哦  不
Oh, no!
不  等等  求你了  不要
No, wait. Please, no.
珍
Jen!
不  不
No! No!
啊  不要
Ah! Don't!
达瑞斯  达瑞斯救我
Darius! Darius, help me!
我很抱歉  我很抱歉
I'm s 0 ry! I'm s 0 ry
不  救我  不拜托
no! Help me! No! Please!
求你了  亲爱的上帝  别这样
Please, dear god. Please don't.
不  不
No! No!
滚开
Fuck off.
听我说
Listen to me.
你在犯错误
You're making a mistake.
你在浪费宝贵的资源
You're wasting valuable resources...
我们在浪费什么
What are we wasting?
我们
Us.
我们  我们
Us. Us.
你有我们
You-you have us.
你能用我们
Use us.
达瑞斯在非营利机构工作
Darius works in nonprofit.
他研究可持续能源  你在搞什么鬼
He works in sustainable energy. What the hell are you doing?
他设计住宅  社区  社区自给自足
He's designed homes, neighborhoods, communities to be self-sufficient.
我们已经自给自足了
We're already self-sufficient.
不  但你需要维修改进
No, but you need maintenance, improvements.
你们这会遭受风暴破坏  气候变化
You suffer storm damage, climate changes.
泉水干涸你需要解决问题
Springs dry up. You need problems solved.
他就是做这个的
That's what he does.
这是他的技能
That's his skill.
这就是他能做的
That's what he can contribute.
你这么做  会失去一切
You do this, you lose all of that.
你很强壮
Standard says you're strong.
你有战士精神
You have a warrior spirit.
我不会放弃
I don't give up.
那你呢
And what of you?
你有什么提议
What do you offer?
我自己
Myself.
我的家族没有疾病
There's no sickness in my family.
没有癌症
No cancer.
我年轻  健康
I'm young, healthy.
我会有强壮健康的孩子
I'll have strong, healthy children.
你手下谁需要妻子
Who among your men needs a wife?
不
No.
张开嘴
Open your mouth.
闭嘴
Shut up.
张开腿
Spread your legs.
伊迪丝
Edith.
你准备好成为忠诚的公民了吗
Are you prepared to become a loyal citizen?
是的
Yes.
你准备好成为忠诚的公民了吗
Are you prepared to become a loyal citizen?
是的
Yes.
如果你跑了  你应该知道下山没有安全的路
If you run, you should know there's no safe way off this mountain.
如果我们的陷阱没能杀死你  动物会的
If our traps don't kill you, the animals will.
如果这片土地不杀你  我们的人会杀你
If the land doesn't kill you, our people will.
如果你不出一份力  你会在这里结束生命
If you don't contribute... You'll end up here.
你们明白了吗
Do you understand?
明白了
Yes.
是啊  明白了
Yeah. Yeah.
请不要恨我
Please don't hate me.
[外语]
Vee nor.
什么意思
Vee nor what?
朋友
"Friends?"
那是朋友的意思吗
Does that mean "friends?"
跟我来
Come with me.
我已经一年没有妻子了
I've had no wife for a year.
她摔死了
She died in a fall.
在这里  人们要嘛死于意外  要嘛老死
Here, people die of either accidents or old age.
我们能走了吗
Can we ever leave?
你为什么要这么做
Why would you want to?
我了解山下的生活
I know about life below.
你孤身一人
You're alone.
人们到山里来找东西
People come to the mountains looking for something.
提醒他们生命是有价值的
Something to remind them that life is worth living.
你是来找东西的
You came looking for something.
现在你找到了
And now you've found it.
你没有你假装的那么坚强
You're not as strong as you pretend to be.
我是珍
Hey, it's Jen.
请留言我会回电
Leave a message, and I'll hit you back.
谢谢  拜
Thanks. Bye.
语音信箱已满
The mailbox is full
现在无法接收讯息  再见
and cannot accept any messages at this time. Goodbye.
你好
Hi.
不  我不知道
No. I don't know.
可能还要几天
Maybe a couple more days.
我在等当地警方的回覆然后再行动
I'm waiting to hear back from the local police before I move on.
我知道
I know.
她失踪了
She's, uh... she's missing.
(鹿啤餐厅)
你好
Hello.
你女儿和她朋友的事我很遗憾
I'm sorry about your daughter and her friends.
双份威士忌  谢谢
Double whiskey. Thank you.
我让她顺着小路走
I told her to stay on the trail.
有人住在那座山上
There are people living on that mountain.
什么人
What people?
创建会
The foundation.
The foundation?
这是一个大家都知道却不说的事
It's a story people here know but don't talk about,
除了偷偷讨论
except in whispers.
就像鬼故事一样
Like a ghost story.
哦
On.
1859年  十几个家庭收拾行李逃上山
In 1859, a dozen or so families packed up and fled up the mountain.
他们害怕美国崩溃  想要保护他们的生活方式
They feared the collapse of America, and wanted to protect their way of life.
他们说当美国沦陷时
They said when America fell,
他们将是建立新国家的基础
they would be the foundation on which a new nation would be built.
这些人的后代
And these descendants of these people
还住在山上吗
are still living up there on the mountain?
我们不打扰他们  他们也不打扰我们
We don't bother them, and they don't bother us.
但如果有人上去了  就再也回不来了
But anyone who goes up there, they don't come back...
无论死活
Alive or dead.
你怎么知道的
And you know this how?
以前也发生过
It's happened before.
但如果以前发生过
But if it's happened before,
为什么没人做点什么
why hasn't someone done something about it?
因为
Because...
看起来像是他们离开了
It's made to look like they left.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
你不听我的话是吧  先生
You just don't listen, do you, mister?
你的女儿死了  你不会想知道还剩下什么
Your girl is dead, and you don't want to find what's left.
她没死
She's not dead.
你个狗娘养的
Oh, you son of a...
等等  等等
Hold on, hold on, hold on, hold on.
嘿
Hey.
Hey!
不  不不
No, no, no.
不不
No! No!
扶他起来  嘿
Get him up. Hey!
你这混蛋
You son of a bitch.
该死
Oh, shit.
你在做什么
What are you doing?
你觉得我会做什么
What does it look like I'm doing?
你不要上去
You don't want to go up there.
她是我女儿  我会找到她的
She's my daughter. I'm gonna find her.
史考特
Scott...
你无法阻止我
And there's nothing you can do to stop me.
上帝啊  怎么了
Jesus. What happened?
你昨晚的伤跟山上他们的手段相比  根本不算什么
Whatever happened to you is nothing compared to what they'll do.
等一下
Wait.
我可以帮你
I could help you.
是他吗
This him?
对
Yes.
艾德  这是肖先生
Ed, this is Mr. Shaw.
艾德是我侄子  他是个猎人
Ed's my nephew. He's a hunter.
你出车祸了吗
You get in a car wreck or something?
别的原因
Or something.
你带钱了吗
You got the money?
五千
Five thousand.
可以
Okay.
那明早见
We'll see you in the morning, then.
不  不
No, no.
我们现在就去
We go now.
你有装备吗
You got gear?
不能穿成这样上去  这不是在休闲
Can't go up there dressed for no ladies' tea.
你需要眼镜吗
You need glasses?
背包  睡袋  拐杖
Backpack, sleeping bag, poles.
好了好了好了  库珀
Okay, okay, okay. Coop.
把我的应急包扔给我
Toss me my go bag.
里面有你需要的一切
I got everything you need in there.
你为什么不去把那件黄外套脱下来
Why don't you go and take that yellow jacket off your back.
你穿着像个靶心一样走来走去
Look like a fucking bull's-eye walking around.
把钥匙给艾琳
Give the keys to Aileen.
她会把你的车停在旅馆外面
She'll park your car outside the inn,
伪装成你整晚都在那里
make it look like you been there all night.
我问你个问题
Hey, let me ask you a question.
你为什么同意这么做
Why'd you agree to do this?
为钱
Money.
我有个儿子想上焊接技术学校
Got a son here I want to send through welding school,
我也不喜欢那些创建会的混蛋
and I ain't got no love for them foundation fuckers.
我中了箭
Arrow did that.
缝了十九针
Nineteen stitches.
警告我远离他们的山
A warning shot across the old brain pan to keep off of their mountain.
我不介意一报还一报
Wouldn't mind returning the favor.
退后
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Stay back.
木桩陷阱
Stake trap.
狡猾的混蛋
Sneaky motherfuckers.
离开小溪
Gget out of the creek.
创建会的人喜欢设这种陷阱
These foundation folks like to set traps like these
逼陌生人下山
to drive strangers up off the mountain.
在我中箭的地方还有第二种陷阱
There's a second set further up where I got my trophy.
第二种会怎么样?
What comes after the second set?
陌生人就活不了
Strangers don't get to leave.
你要跟着我的脚步走
You walk where I walk.
上帝啊
Jesus.
还有多远
How much further?
山脊上有条陡峭的小路
There's a steep trail up along this Ridge.
但我不会撒谎  这段路可不好走
I won't lie, though. It's a bitch of a hike.
但这能让我们直接找到那混蛋的前门
But it shortcuts us right up to the bastards' front door.
库珀  库珀
Cooper! Cooper!
库珀  你受伤了吗
Cooper, you hurt?
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我好像扭到脚踝了
I think I twisted my ankle.
天啊  来帮我把他拉出来
Christ. Come on, help me pull him out.
好了把手给我
Okay, give me your hand.
另一只手给我
Give me your other hand.
加油加油
Come on. Come on.
加油
Come on.
什么
What?
库珀
Cooper?
上帝啊
Jesus.
一步一步来
One step at a time.
达瑞斯
Darius?
是我
Uh, it's me.
珍在哪
Where's Jen?
你怎么了
What's happened to you?
这他妈是怎么回事
What the fuck is happening?
我女儿呢
Where's my daughter?
退后
Stay back.
你们这些人怎么回事
What's wrong with you people?
珍
Jen?
Jen.
他们对你做了什么
What have they done to you?
你对我女儿做了什么
What have you done to my daughter?
不管你是谁  这个女人不是你女儿
Whoever you are... This woman is not your daughter.
她是我妻子
She's my wife.
你说什么呢
What are you talking about?
这他妈是什么情况
What the fuck is that?
不需要庭审
No trial is necessary.
我们认为这个陌生人非法入侵
We find this stranger guilty of trespassing.
判决是黑暗  黎明执行
The sentence is darkness, to be carried out at dawn.
你什么意思
What are you saying?
嘿  啊
Hey... ah!
你逃不掉的
You won't get away with this.
人们会来找我的
People will come for me.
他们知道我在哪
They know where I am!
不  没人会来的
No. No one will ever come.
珍妮弗
Jennifer!
你还好吗
Are you all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
怎么了
Why?
那个人是你父亲
That man is your father.
我已经做出了选择
I've made my choice.
珍  嘘
Jen. Shh.
我们时间不多了
We don't have much time.
你找到了上来的路  你知道回去哪条路安全吗
You found your way up here. Do you know a safe way back?
可以
Okay.
走吧
Let's go.
你用箭射了我
You shot me with an arrow.
不然他们会把我们俩都杀了
They would've killed us both.
来吧  我们走
Come on, let's go.
这是干什么
What is this?
该走了
Time to leave.
为什么是现在
Why now?
因为明天早上他们会杀了我爸爸
Because tomorrow morning, they're gonna kill my dad.
我们得走了
We need to go.
来吧
Come on.
我不去了
I'm not going.
什么
What?
这些人看清我了
These people see me.
我属于他们
I belong to them.
他们属于我
They belong to me.
去吧
(50.
我不会阻止你的
I won't stop you.
你真的觉得你能回到过去的生活吗
Do you really think you can go back to your old life?
跟紧我
Stay close.
这扇门从没像这样锁过
This gate's never locked like this.
珍
Jen.
露丝
Ruthie.
我得走了
I have to go.
你明白吗
Do you understand?
我知道你有时候喜欢偷偷下山
I know you like to sneak down the mountain sometimes.
你知道另一条出口吗
Do you know another way out?
穿过那里
Through there?
你是说那里有出口
You're saying there's a way out through there?
你想跟我一起走吗  露丝
Do you want to come with me, ruthie?
你想的话就可以
You can if you want to.
走吧
Let's go.
天啊
Aw, geez.
大白天的我都差点没上来
I barely made it up here in the daylight.
嘘
Shh!
你听到了吗
Did you hear that?
珍
Jen!
爸爸
Dad.
珍
Jen?
我能闻到你的味道
I can smell your juices.
等温尼伯夺走你的眼睛  耳朵和舌头
After venable takes your eyes, your ears, and your tongue,
我要把你据为己有
I'm going to keep you for myself.
珍
Jen.
Jen?
珍
Jen.
珍妮弗
Jennifer.
好吧
All right.
嘿
Hey.
我们现在怎么办
What do we do now?
现在最重要的是做出下一个选择
All that matters now is the next choice.
这就是我在这座山上学到的
That's what I've learned on this mountain.
我就是这样活下来的
That's how I've survived.
走吧
Let's go.
哪条路
Which way?
我说过会再见到你的
Told you I'd see you again.
给我退后
Back the fuck up!
等一下  我们是来帮忙的
Whoa, wait a minute. We're here to help.
胡扯  操你妈
Bullshit. And fuck you, too.
先生  我之前是想救你的命
Hey, mister, I was trying to save your life back there.
我觉得好好揍你一顿  你就能卷铺盖走人了
I figured a good beat down might send your ass packing.
而你
And you.
我黄色的眼眸
That yellow in my eyes...
是我的肝脏在折磨我
Was my liver turning on me.
你是对的
You were right.
我没有孩子
Look, I ain't got any kids.
但我侄子六年前在这片树林里失踪了
But my nephew disappeared in these woods six years ago.
我一直没找到他的尸体
And I never found the body.
该死的创建会
Fucking foundation.
我真想一枪崩了那些混蛋
I'd like to shoot every one of those sons of bitches.
你的朋友们呢
Where's your friends?
只有我们了
It's just us.
那我们带你们下山吧
Well, then, let's get you the hell off this mountain.
来吧
Come on.
啊
Ah!
妈的  不  不  不
Fuck! No, no, no!
我会打死你的  他在哪
I'll get you. Where the fuck is it?
我想我们干掉他们了
I think we got 'em.
快快快快
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
珍妮弗
Jennifer!
上车
Get in the truck.
Get in.
这是我叔公威利的特殊配方
It's my great-uncle Willie's special recipe.
好吧  随你便
All right, suit yourself.
我想在明晚之前做好准备
I want to set that footing by tomorrow evening.
是啊  亲爱的  嘿  老爸
Yeah. Hi, sweetie. Hey, dad.
我给你带来了修改后的
I brought you the revised blueprints
北考德威尔住宅蓝图  你开玩笑吧
for the north Caldwell house. Oh, you're kidding.
你没必要带到这里来
You didn't need to bring them all the way down here.
我知道你想马上看
I know you wanted to see them right away.
我还知道你会讨厌新的主浴室
I also know you're gonna hate the new master bath.
你是有警告过我
Well, you did warn me.
嗯哼
Mm-hm.
怎么了
What?
没什么我真为你骄傲
Nothing. I'm just proud of you.
谢了  老爸
Thanks, dad.
抱一下
Come on.
我爱你
I love you.
我也爱你
I love you, too.
晚安
Well, good night.
回家见
I'll see you at home.
记住  今晚是披萨和电影之夜
Oh, and remember, it's pizza and movie night,
所以别迟到了
so don't be late.
男孩们选了《食人族家族》
The boys picked something with inbred cannibals?
又一次
Again?
天啊
Geez.
这是隐藏荧幕
It's a privacy screen.
哦  是啊
Oh. Yeah.
从侧面看不到
You can't see it from the side.
好了开始吧
All right, here we go.
亲爱的
Oh, hi, hon.
来见见我们的新邻居  约翰和露丝
Uh, meet our new neighbors, John and ruthie.
他们在看街尾的卡普兰房子
They're looking at the kaplan house down the street.
都还没定下来
Nothing is set in stone yet.
原来约翰认识史考特
Well, it turns out John knows Scott.
我们有过交集
Our paths crossed.
他说如果我来附近的话  可以来见见他的家人
Said if I was ever in the neighborhood to stop by and meet the family.
世界真小  对吧
Small world, right?
对  非常小
Yes. Very.
你要把东西放下吗
Are you going to put those groceries down?
科琳
Corinne...
这咖啡太好喝了  谢谢
This coffee is wonderful, thank you.
你们能留下来吃晚餐吗
Uh, can you stay for dinner?
史考特肯定很想见你
I'm sure Scott would love to see you.
我们要吃披萨
We're having pizza.
好
Yes.
我们很乐意留下
We would love to stay.
我们开了很久的车
It's been a long drive.
谢谢你  我马上回来
Thank you. Oh, be right back.
我看出来你怀了双胞胎
And I see you're eating for two.
祝贺你
Congratulations.
我要上厕所
I need to use the bathroom.
滚出我家  珍
Get the fuck out of my house. Jen!
放下武器  不然我就杀了你全家
Put your weapon down, or I kill your family.
我看错你了  珍
I was wrong about you, Jen.
你很强悍
You are strong.
如果我想离开你  我就必须强悍
I had to be if I was ever gonna get away from you.
现在该回家了
Now it's time to come home.
有什么意义呢  你会杀了我
What's the point? You have to kill me.
对
Yes.
但要等到我们的孩子出生
But not until our child is born.
恭喜你  奶奶
Congratulations, grandma.
珍
Jen...
你在做什么
What are you doing?
珍
Jen?
妈妈
Mom?
你和男孩们能回避一下吗
Can you and the boys excuse us?
约翰是来谈生意的
John's here to talk business.
当然可以  来吧  小蓝
Of course. Come on. Laundry.
来吧  你想吃披萨吗  小迷糊
Come on. You want pizza? Mush.
我看错你了珍
I was wrong about you, Jen.
你很强悍
You are strong.
如果我想离开你  我必须强悍
I had to be if I was ever gonna get away from you.
你使我们让你变得很强悍
You let us make you strong.
很好
That's good.
你怀了我的孩子所以
You're carrying my child, so...
该回家了
Time to come home.
向我保证你不会伤害他们
Promise me you won't hurt them.
永远不会
Fver.
你再也不会回来了
You'll never come back here.
向我保证  我就跟你一起去
Promise, and I'll go with you.
我向你保证
You have my word.